Guide to the Office of Student Activities and Facilities Records, 1936-ongoing UA.09.05.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA 82-58, 1955-1980, 5 boxes
  - Facilities, Committee on the Use of, 1970-1977 (Box 8)
  - Facilities Council (for Union and Flowers), 1963-1979 (Box 8)
  - "Fact Sheet": Student Activities, Office of, Records, 1974-1978 (Box 8)
  - Faculty ledger account correspondence, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Fencing Club, 1977-1979 (Box 8)
  - Financial aid notices, 1976-1979 (Box 8)
  - Flying Club--charter file, permanent, 1976-1977 (Box 8)
  - Folksong Society--charter file, permanent, 1972-1976 (Box 8)
  - Follow-up report forms, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Forum for Advancement of Students in Science and Technology--charter file, permanent, 1974-1977 (Box 8)
  - Freewater Films--loan agreement, 1971-1975 (Box 8)
  - Freshman Houses--damage accounts, 1970-1971 (Box 8)
  - Freshman Week, 1972-1976 (Box 8)
  - Fund raising projects, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Gamers Club--charter file, permanent, 1976-1977 (Box 8)
  - Graduate Students Association--correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 8)
  - Graphic Products, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Gross receipts tax form, 1972 (Box 8)
  - House damage accounts, 1972 (Box 8)
  - IBM, 1974 (Box 8)
  - IFC functions, 1971-1972 (Box 9)
  - International League for Animal Protection charter file, 1973-1976 (Box 9)
  - Inventory control sheets, 1975-1977 (Box 9)
  - IRI, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Jazz Ensemble charter file, 1971-1975 (Box 9)
  - Job descriptions, 1972-1976 (Box 9)
  - Joe Baldwin Committee charter file, 1974-1977 (Box 9)
  - Jordan Student Center, 1973-1979 (Box 9)
  - Kappa Alpha Theta, 1971 (Box 9)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Key request, 1969-1976 (Box 9)
  - Kyokushin Kaikaw (Karate) Club, 1974-1978 (Box 9)
  - Latent Image 4, 1973-1979, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Leadership training, 1972-1976 (Box 9)
  - Loan requests, 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - Mailing lists, 1974 (Box 9)
  - Manuals, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Material Support Dept., 1975 (Box 9)
  - Minister to the University, Office of, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Minority Conference, 1976-1979 (Box 9)
  - Mirecourt House, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous, 1974-1980 (Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous organizations, 1971-1979 (Box 9)
  - Model United Nations Group--charter file, 1973 (Box 9)
  - National Association of Student Personnel Administrators (NASPA), 1973-1979, 4 folders (Box 9)
  - NASPA newsletters, 1976-1979 (Box 9)
  - NASPA Task Force on Ethnic Minorities, 1974-1978, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - National On-Campus Report, 1977 (Box 9)
  - New American Movement, 1974-1975 (Box 9)
  - Newspaper articles, 1974 (Box 9)
  - North Carolina Central University (NCCU), 1975-1978 (Box 9)
  - Office budget, 1969-1979 (Box 9)
  - Officers of student organizations, 1977-1979 (Box 9)
  - Orchid Society, 1976-1978 (Box 9)
  - Organization audits and budget requests, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Orthodox Students' Association, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Parcheesi Society, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Parents' Weekend, 1974-1976 (Box 9)
  - Pep Board, 1970 (Box 9)
  - Performance evaluation, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Phi Delta Theta loan agreement, 1971-1975 (Box 9)
  - Phi Kappa Sigma loan agreement, 1974-1976 (Box 9)
  - Pi Kappa Phi loan agreement, 1970-1972 (Box 9)
  - PolyCom Associates, undated (Box 9)
  - Portage, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Post office rentals, 1975-1979 (Box 9)
  - PRAXIS/Socialist Action Union, 1970 (Box 9)
  - President's Council on Black Affairs--minutes and miscellaneous, 1976-1979 (Box 9)
  - Programming--films, 1970-1978 (Box 9)
  - Programmatic staff, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Progressive Political Union, 1978 (Box 9)
  - "Provost's Agreements," Student Activities, Office of. Records, ca. 1978-19791978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Publications Board, 1970-1980, 13 folders (Box 10)
    Budgets, chairmen, charter, meetings, progress reports, and other materials.
  - Publications Enterprise, 1970-1974 (Box 10)
  - Publicity Committee, 1977 (Box 10)
  - Quad forms, completed, 1974-1979 (Box 10)
  - Racial Understanding, Committee for, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Radical Academic Union, 1974-1977 (Box 10)
  - Recruitment (minority), 1975 (Box 10)
  - Reading Center Club, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Registrar, Office of the, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Renaissance Universal Club, 1976-1977 (Box 10)
  - Reorganization Educational Adm., 1979 (Box 10)
  - Request approved, 1976-1977 (Box 10)
  - Request approved, 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Request pending, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
  - Reservation forms, completed, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Responsibilities and organizations, office (Doug Jensen), 1974 (Box 10)
  - Revised short-termed pooled investment forms, 1976 (Box 10)
  - Room reservation policy, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
  - Share Your Christmas, 1975-1978 (Box 10)
  - Skeet Club, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Social Implications of Duke's Investment Policies, Committee on the, 1977-1979 (Box 10)
  - Squash Club, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Star Graphics, Inc., 1974-1976 (Box 10)
  - Student Activities Office, 1955-1980, 31 folders
    - Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Car and van, 1973-1978, 5 folders (Box 10)
    - Key log, undated (Box 10)
    - Mimeo, 1974-1980 (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1977-1980 (Box 10)
    - Operating account, 1955-1978, 10 folders (Box 10)
      Inactive files, loans, special events, and transfer journal vouchers.
    - Space assignments, undated (Box 10)
    - Summer activities, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Surveys, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Telephone bills, 1975-1978 (Box 10)
    - Telephone codes, 1968-1975 (Box 10)
    - Telephone correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 10)
    - Telephone directory information, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Telephone logs, 1971-1978, 4 folders (Box 10)
    - Vouchers, 1968-1969 (Box 10)
  - Student Affairs New Student Assembly1978 (Box 10)
  - Student Affairs Restructuring Committee, 1974- 1974 (Box 10)
  - Student Affairs staff, 1975-1978 (Box 10)
  - Student/Faculty Cooperative Movement, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Students for Music at Duke, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Student International Meditation Society, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Student Migrant Action Coalition--charter file, 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Student publications, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Summer activities, 1973-1978 (Box 11)
  - Summer Appalachian Project, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Summer Organization Bulletin, 1975-1978 (Box 11)
  - Summer Programming Committee, 1972-1979 (Box 11)
  - Summer Transitional Program, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
  - Teacher-course evaluation research information, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Time sheets and records, 1974-1975, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Transportation Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
  - T.V. Club, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Union Board, 1972-1976 (Box 11)
  - University Center--new, undated (Box 11)
  - University policy changes, 1974-1980 (Box 11)
  - Van policy, undated (Box 11)
  - Wage and Salary, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
  - WDUR, WDBS, WDUK, 1973-1978 (Box 11)
  - Wind Symphony--charter file, 1972-1978 (Box 11)
  - Windsor House, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Women's Alliance, 1973-1975 (Box 11)
  - Women's Liberation, 1970-1972 (Box 11)
  - Women's Rugby, 1979 (Box 11)
  - YM-YWCA, 1970-1978, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Yoga Association, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Young Democrats, 1970-1977 (Box 11)
  - Youth Caucus, Americans for Democratic Action, undated (Box 11)
  - Youth Outreach, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Zoology Majors' Union, undated (Box 11)
- Accession UA 82-110, 1966-1982, 2 boxes
  Rules and regulations on alcohol, drugs, sales on campus, use of facilities for public events; WDBS; black student organizations; and others.
  - Afro-American Studies, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Alpha Tau Omega--loan agreement, 1975-1978 (Box 11)
  - Association of African Students--budget, charter, and correspondence files, 1968-1980 (Box 11)
  - Bacchus's Gift--charter file, 1981 (Box 11)
  - Baha'i Club--budget and charter files, 1973-1978 (Box 11)
  - Bassett Committee--funds, 1975-1976 (Box 11)
  - Class of 1981, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Club Office lists, undated (Box 11)
  - Community Environmental Education thru Duke (C.E.E.D)--budget and charter files, 1976-1979 (Box 11)
  - Dance Black, 1976-1977 (Box 11)
  - Duke Anti-Klan Coalition, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Duke Jewish Forum, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
  - Duke Players--correspondence, 1970-1978 (Box 11)
  - Duke Students for John Anderson, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Energy Efficient Vehicle--budget and charter files, 1978-1980 (Box 11)
  - Facilities Available to Org. Regulations, 1970-1973 (Box 11)
  - Flowers-Page, undated (Box 11)
  - German Club--charter file, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Human Survival Caravan at Duke (H.U.S.C.A.D)--budget and charter files, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
  - IFC-Panhellenic All Campus Carnival--budget and charter files, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Karamu, 1975-1982 (Box 11)
  - Kung Fu Club--budget and charter files, 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Management Science Majors Union--budget and charter files, 1978-1982 (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 1970-1982 (Box 11)
  - N.C. Korean Christian Students Association, 1981 (Box 11)
  - Officers, mailing lists, 1980-1982 (Box 11)
  - Organization for Life, Choice, and Equity (DOLCE)--charter file, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Philosophy Club--charter file, 1981 (Box 11)
  - Political Science Union--budget and charter files, 1970-1981 (Box 11)
  - Pre-Medical Society--charter and correspondence files, 1960-1981 (Box 11)
  - Prometheus Black, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Rules and Regulations, 1966-1977, 11 folders
    - Alcoholic beverages, 1970-1975 (Box 11)
    - Beer Blasts and similar events, 1974-1977 (Box 11)
    - Duke political groups policy, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
    - Duke quad parties, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Duke raffles policy, 1972 (Box 11)
    - Duke recruitment, 1968-1972 (Box 11)
    - Duke sales policy, 1972-1976 (Box 11)
    - Drugs policy, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Firearms policy, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Information and regulations of Duke University, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Student rights and freedoms statements, 1966-1969 (Box 11)
  - Society of Physics Students, 1981 (Box 11)
  - Sociology Majors Union--budget and charter files, 1976-1981 (Box 11)
  - Southern Africa Coalition--budget and charter files, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
  - Soviet Jewry Task Force--budget and charter files, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
  - Sport Parachuting Club--budget and charter files, 1972-1975 (Box 11)
  - Students for the Advancement of Bioethics--budget and charter files, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
  - Union Building, undated (Box 11)
  - WDBS, 1972-1975 (Box 11)
  - Women's Softball Club--budget, charter, and correspondence files, 1980-1982 (Box 11)
  - Ledger: Receipts and Disbursement, Student Organizations, 1969-1978 (Box 12)
- Accession UA 87-3, 1970-1986, 1 boxes
  Club sports financial files; Jordan Center reservations and correspondence.
  - Aikido Club, 1981-1983 (Box 13)
  - Audits and budgets, 1984-1986 (Box 13)
  - Badminton Club--correspondence, 1972-1985 (Box 13)
  - Baseball, 1982-1986 (Box 13)
  - Cyclist League--correspondence, 1971-1985 (Box 13)
  - Duke Crew--charter file, 1975-1981 (Box 13)
  - Duke Crew--correspondence, 1975-1986 (Box 13)
  - Duke Tennis Club, 1975-1985 (Box 13)
  - Duke Women's Track Club, 1978-1985 (Box 13)
  - Equestrian Club, 1981-1985 (Box 13)
  - Female Affiliates of Duke Soccer, 1978-1982 (Box 13)
  - Fencing Club--correspondence, 1979-1985 (Box 13)
  - Field Hockey, 1982-1984 (Box 13)
  - Football Club--charter and correspondence files, 1970-1985 (Box 13)
  - Golf Club, 1982-1985 (Box 13)
  - Graduate Soccer Club, 1980-1981 (Box 13)
  - Ice Hockey, 1975-1986 (Box 13)
  - Jordan Center--correspondence file, 1975-1984, 2 folders (Box 13)
    Contained oversize blueprints, now housed in Box 12.
  - Jordan Center reservation books and forms, 1982-1984, 4 folders (Box 13)
  - Karate Club, 1983-1985 (Box 13)
  - Lacrosse Club, 1978-1986 (Box 13)
  - Men's Crew--correspondence file, 1980-1986 (Box 13)
  - Men's Gymnastics Club, 1978-1984 (Box 13)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 1982-1986 (Box 13)
  - Roadrunners, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Rugby Club, 1973-1985 (Box 13)
  - Sailing Club, 1970-1985 (Box 13)
  - Sailing Club--completed waiver forms, 1973-1978, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - SCC Allocations, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Soccer League--correspondence, 1974-1985 (Box 13)
  - Softball Club, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Sports Clubs--budgets, 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Sports Club Council (SCC) Handbook for Club Presidents, 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Table Tennis Club, 1975-1985 (Box 13)
  - Tae Kwon Do, 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Volleyball Club--correspondence file, 1979-1985 (Box 13)
  - Water Polo Club--correspondence file, 1978-1985 (Box 13)
  - Women's Crew-- correspondence, 1981-1986 (Box 13)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1980-1986 (Box 13)
  - Women's Tennis Club--correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 13)
- Accessions UA 88-34 and UA 89-82, 1968-1988, 3 boxes
  Student Organizations, in alphabetical order (as received).
  - ACP Convention/ Publication Board, 1981 (Box 13)
  - Alpha Cubic: Alabama Appreciation Association, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Alternatives for Youth in Durham (AYD)--charter, 1981-1984 (Box 13)
  - Amateur Radio Association--charter file, 1973-1981 (Box 13)
  - American Field Service Club--budget and charter files, 1972-1982 (Box 13)
  - Americans for Progress--charter file, 1984 (Box 13)
  - American Society of Personnel Administrators, 1982-1983 (Box 13)
  - Arab-American Association--charter file, 1975-1981 (Box 13)
  - Archaeology Club--charter file, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Archery Club--charter file, 1974-1981 (Box 13)
  - Arms Control Study Group--charter file, 1982-1983 (Box 13)
  - ASDU, 1977-1985, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 13)
  - ASDU, 1977-1985, Folder 2-3 of 3 (Box 14)
  - ASDU Transfer Student Committee, 1982-1986 (Box 14)
  - Association of Computing Machinery--charter file, 1975-1985 (Box 14)
  - Association of Duke Women--charter file, 1979-1983 (Box 14)
  - Association for Independent Houses--charter file, 1969-1982 (Box 14)
  - Baha'i Club, 1986 (Box 14)
  - Bioethics Forum, 1979-1982 (Box 14)
  - Black student Weekend, 1982-1983 (Box 14)
  - Bread for the World, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Coalition for Alternative to Shearon Harris (CASH), 1986 (Box 14)
  - Chanticleer, 1983-1984 (Box 14)
  - Chronicle, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Class of '85, 1982-1984 (Box 14)
  - Colorblind?, 1986 (Box 14)
  - Committee for Serina WuDunn Memorial Scholarship, 1984-1986 (Box 14)
  - Conference on the Future of North Carolina National Forests, undated (Box 14)
  - Council on Presidents, 1981 (Box 14)
  - Duke Connection, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Duke Discordian Alliance, 1986 (Box 14)
  - Duke/Durham Day, 1984-1985 (Box 14)
  - Duke Engineer, 1985-1987 (Box 14)
  - Duke Wargamer's--charter file, 1981 (Box 14)
  - DUMB, undated (Box 14)
  - Economics Majors Union--budget file, 1978-1981 (Box 14)
  - Energy Action Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 14)
  - Engineering Promotion Council, 1983 (Box 14)
  - English Majors Union, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Equestrian Club--charter file, 1978-1985 (Box 14)
  - Field Hockey Club, 1985-1986 (Box 14)
  - First Ranger Company--charter file, 1982-1985 (Box 14)
  - Free Speech Club, 1986 (Box 14)
  - Freedom Music Initiative, 1986 (Box 14)
  - French Club, 1985-1986 (Box 14)
  - Freshmen Orientation, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Friendship Festival--charter, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Frisbee Club, 1977-1985 (Box 14)
  - Gay Alliance--charter file, 1972-1986 (Box 14)
  - Health Sciences Association, 1983 (Box 14)
  - High Technology--correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 14)
  - Homecoming Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 14)
  - Inter-View Magazine, 1983-1984 (Box 14)
  - Karate Club, 1973-1985 (Box 14)
  - Men's Football, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Mini Baja Construction Club--charter file, 1982-1984 (Box 14)
  - Nereidians--budget file, 1980-1986 (Box 14)
  - North Carolina Action for Farmworkers, 1982-1984 (Box 14)
  - North Carolina Student Legislature--budget and charter files, 1970-1986 (Box 14)
  - North Carolina Student Legislature--correspondence file, 1970-1984 (Box 14)
  - Okinawa Kenpo Karate Kobudo, 1984-1986 (Box 14)
  - Partners in Psychiatry--charter, 1982-1983 (Box 14)
  - Peacemaking in a Nuclear Age, 1982-1985 (Box 14)
  - Project for Understanding the Rural South--charter file, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Provost Agreement, 1968-1982, 3 folders (Box 14)
  - Publications Board, 1980-1985, 4 folders (Box 14)
  - Publication Board--budget, 1979-1980 (Box 14)
  - Publication Board--minutes, 1980-1982 (Box 14)
  - Referral file and information, 1977-1984 (Box 14)
  - Save the Efe Pygmies, 1982-1983 (Box 14)
  - Scuba Club--budget and charter files, 1973-1985 (Box 14)
  - Scuba Club--completed waiver forms, 1979 (Box 14)
  - Scuba Club--records, 1979-1985 (Box 14)
  - Share Your Christmas, 1984-1987 (Box 14)
  - Sherlockian Society--charter file, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Signs of Silence, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Skydevils, 1972-1985 (Box 15)
  - Society for Culture, Illness, and Healing, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Society for Religious Understanding, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Student Activity Day, 1984-1986, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Student Affairs Leadership Assistance Program (SALAP), 1981-1987, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - SALAP--correspondence, 1984-1988, 4 folders (Box 15)
  - Students against World Hunger, 1981-1983 (Box 15)
  - Students for Albert Gore for President, 1987-1988 (Box 15)
  - Students for a Middle East Understanding--charter file, 1982-1985 (Box 15)
  - Students for Bob Dole, 1987-1988 (Box 15)
  - Duke Students for Broyhill, 1986 (Box 15)
  - Students for Energy Conservation, 1982-1986 (Box 15)
  - Students for Gephardt, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Students for Hunt--charter file, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Students for Jack Kemp, 1987-1988 (Box 15)
  - Students for Sanford, 1986 (Box 15)
  - Student Transfer Committee--charter file, 1981-1985 (Box 15)
  - Union Board, 1983-1988, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - United Students Against Apartheid, 1987 (Box 15)
  - United Students of America, 1983-1987 (Box 15)
  - Women for Peace and Justice--charter file, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Women's Softball, 1981-1985 (Box 15)
- Accessions UA 89-85, UA 91-106, and UA 92-19, 1980-1988, 2 boxes
  Predominantly legislative files from ASDU (Associated Students of Duke University); also contains income statements from various organizations, files about Black Student Weekends from the mid-1980s, and miscellaneous other documents. Three small accessions have been combined and arranged in alphabetical order by topic; specific accession numbers are indicated on the folders.
  - Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU), 1980-1988, 12 folders (Box 15)
    - "ASDU Communicator," 1982 (Box 15)
    - Bylaw proposals and charter notices, 1986-1987 (Box 15)
    - Legislative packets, 1986-1987 (Box 15)
    - Legislature--membership, 1980 (Box 15)
    - Legislature--minutes, 1982-1988, 7 folders (Box 15)
  - Black Student Weekend, 1984-1987, Folder 1 of 4 (Box 15)
  - Black Student Weekend, 1984-1987, Folder 2-4 of 4 (Box 16)
  - Copy Shop, 1981-1985 (Box 16)
  - Electronic news service, 1983-1984 (Box 16)
  - Income statements--student organizations, 1983-1987, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - Student Affairs Development Screening Committee, 1985-1986, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Union Board, 1985-1986 (Box 16)
- Accession UA 90-24, 1968-1989, 3 boxes
  Correspondence, memoranda, minutes, and financial records concerning student organizations, with bulk dates 1982-1987. Includes ASDU legislative and executive minutes, charter application and charters, Bassett Fund requisitions, and folders on student organizations and activities.
  - Admissions Program/ Student Affairs Presentation, 1987-1988 (Box 16)
  - Alpha Phi Omega--charter file, 1968-1987, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - American Society of Civil Engineers, 1975-1988 (Box 16)
  - American Society of Mechanical Engineers--budget file, 1976-1986 (Box 16)
  - Archive--correspondence file, 1970-1988 (Box 16)
  - Arnold Air Society--budget file, 1976-1987 (Box 16)
  - ASDU, 1977-1988, 10 folders
    - Associated Students of Duke University, 1977-1986 (Box 16)
    - Applications and forms, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
    - Audits, 1979-1988 (Box 16)
    - Committee representatives and responsibilities, 1979-1981 (Box 16)
    - Dining halls, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
    - Minutes, 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Minutes and miscellaneous, 1979-1986 (Box 16)
    - SOC, 1985-1987 (Box 16)
    - SOC allocations, 1986-1987 (Box 16)
  - Bassett Committee, 1981-1985 (Box 16)
  - Bassett Fund, 1982-1986, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Black Student Alliance, 1978-1989 (Box 17)
  - BSA concert--Angie Bofill, 1979-1981 (Box 17)
  - Chronicle, 1970-1986, 7 folders
    - Bension Press, 1976-1977 (Box 17)
    - Budget file, 1970-1986 (Box 17)
    - Charter file, 1977-1984 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1982 (Box 17)
    - Courier Times, Inc. and Hinton Press, Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 17)
    - Investments, 1978-1982 (Box 17)
    - Stone Printing Co., 1977 (Box 17)
  - Club officers, 1983-1985, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Commando Group--charter file, 1982 (Box 17)
  - Duke Esperanto, 1987-1988 (Box 17)
  - Duke Gaming Club (DRAGO), 1980-1987 (Box 17)
  - Duke Hillel--budget file, 1967-1986 (Box 17)
  - Duke Network--charter file, 1982-1986 (Box 17)
  - Duke Players, 1985-1989 (Box 17)
  - Duke Students for Ron Paul, 1988 (Box 17)
  - Duke Sufism Club, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Duke Young Democrats--budget file, 1977-1985 (Box 17)
  - DUMB--charter file, 1972-1986 (Box 17)
  - ECOS--correspondence, 1970-1989 (Box 17)
  - English Majors Union--charter file, 1978-1983 (Box 17)
  - Engineering Student Government--budget file, 1970-1985 (Box 17)
  - Geology Club, 1974-1985 (Box 17)
  - German Club, 1984-1986 (Box 17)
  - History Majors Union--charter file, 1975-1986 (Box 17)
  - Hoof 'n' Horn, 1970-1987, 3 folders (Box 17)
    Contains blueprints.
  - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE)--budget file, 1978-1986 (Box 17)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council, 1970-1989 (Box 17)
  - International Association, 1970-1988, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Investment Club--charter file, 1981-1988 (Box 17)
  - Judo Club, 1982-1984 (Box 17)
  - Macintosh User Group--charter file, 1985-1987 (Box 17)
  - Music Association--budget file, 1980-1984 (Box 17)
  - NC Public Interest Research Group (PIRG), 1972-1985 (Box 17)
  - NC PIRG--NC PIRG Advocate and reports, 1972-1975 (Box 17)
  - Outing Club, 1971-1985 (Box 17)
  - Project Wild--correspondence file, 1975-1986 (Box 17)
  - Student Activities Day, 1987-1989 (Box 18)
  - Student Alliance, 1987 (Box 18)
  - Students Concerned About Negligence with Drugs and Alcohol (SCANDAL), 1986 (Box 18)
  - Students for the Explanation and Education of the National High School Model United Nations (SEENHSMUN), 1985 (Box 18)
  - Student National Medical Association--charter file, 1981-1985 (Box 18)
- Accession UA 92-61, 1982-1991, 1 boxes
  Includes files on student community service and volunteer activities, including studies and statistics of these activities; files concerning the Student Affairs Leadership Assistance Program (aka, "Provosts' Agreement"); files of Alpha Phi Omega PALS program, Duke-Africa Initiative, et al.
  - Admissions Program/ Student Affairs Presentation, 1987-1990 (Box 18)
  - Black Student Weekend, 1987-1990 (Box 18)
  - Down Under (Duke Community Service Center), 1989-1991 (Box 18)
  - SALAP, 1986-1990, 3 folders (Box 18)
  - SALAP--forms, 1986-1988 (Box 18)
  - Senior Leadership Awards, 1990 (Box 18)
  - Share Your Christmas, 1989 (Box 18)
  - Student Activities--miscellaneous, 1985-1991 (Box 18)
  - Volunteer Services, 1982-1990 (Box 18)
  - Volunteer Service Fair, 1987-1990 (Box 18)
- Accessions UA 93-137, UA 93-140, and UA 94-44, 1969-1993, 3 boxes
  UA 93-137 (1969-1991): Memoranda, reports, printed mater, correspondence, and other materials concerning residential life, energy management, and office operations; bulk dates 1980-1987.
  UA 93-140 (1982-1993): records of the East Campus Enhancement Committee, 1990-1991, including its final report, June 1991.; faculty associates of student groups, 1982/83; space, parties, etc. Multiculturalism task force, 1989-1991.